adperfect.com 2012-05-29

# AdPerfect - Privacy Policy

## AdPerfect Website Privacy Policy

AdPerfect has created this Privacy Policy statement to document and communicate its commitment to doing business with the highest ethical standards and appropriate internal controls.

We respect your privacy. Information you entrust to AdPerfect will be handled with the greatest care. AdPerfect will not use any information in ways which users did not consent. AdPerfect follows all policies as required by law. 

### Policy Scope

#### Sites Covered by this Policy

This Privacy Policy applies to the AdPerfect website, url [www.adperfect.com.](http://www.adperfect.com/)

#### Effective Locations

This policy applies to Worldwide customers and users.

#### Links to other sites

There may be links posted on AdPerfect’s website that direct the user to a site, other than AdPerfect’s. AdPerfect will only post links that are not harmful and will do so in a lawful manner. When a user navigates to another site, AdPerfect’s Privacy Policy no longer applies to that users use.

### Website Information Gathering

AdPerfect recognizes the importance of keeping the information we collect about you confidential. We always take great care to protect what you entrust to us. AdPerfect is committed to protecting the privacy of visitors to our website.

### Personal Information Gathering

We do not automatically collect personally identifiable information (PII) about our web site visitors. We may record the Internet protocol (IP) address of the computer you are using, the browser software used, the operating systems used, and the websites from which our visitors link directly to our site. We aggregate and use this information to determine how many visitors we have to different pages on our website, to detect and correct system problems, and to improve the usability of our website. This information is not connected to individual names or personal identities.

### Explicit Information Gathering

You can examine our entire website without providing any information whatsoever. Our website’s request a demo form requires users to provide us contact information. The information in this form, and all similar forms, is used to provide information to those who inquire about our solutions and to handle related business matters. This information is also used to get in touch with customers when necessary. The information gathered through this site may be used to notify you about solutions we think will be of interest to you.

### Covert Information Gathering

Our site does not covertly capture information regarding the specific activities of any particular user. We do not have any arrangements with any other sites to track or monitor user activities on the Web. Our site does, however, produce reports that permit us to view your activity on our site in anonymous or aggregated form. We do not use cookies, web bugs, or any other active content mechanism to capture or maintain information about users without their prior consent.

The only personal information that we capture has been submitted to us by the user. 

We do not store any persistent information on your computer. 

### Cookies and Web Bugs

At this time, we do not use cookies on this site. If this changes, this policy statement will be updated to disclose how AdPerfect uses cookies and for what purpose(s).

### Personal Information Usage

When you disclose personal information to us it stays with us. The only exception involves disclosure to the government according to normal business practice, for instance for the collection of taxes, and according to the orders of acourt. For example responding to a subpoena or search warrant.

We do not sell, rent, trade, lend, or otherwise transfer such personal information to affiliates, subsidiaries, sister companies, holding companies, strategic partners, or any other organization, unless specified with the user.

### Children

#### Precautions For Children

AdPerfect does not attempt to collect personal information from children, and does not provide services to children. The AdPerfect website is not directed to children under age 18, and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under age 18. If a child sends personal information to us, and this information can be identified as originating from a child, the information will be deleted. We cannot always determine which information originates with a user that is a child. We do not maintain databases about children.

### Website Security

#### Security Measures

Our site is protected with a variety of security measures including but not limited to change control procedures, passwords, and physical access controls. We also employ a variety of other mechanisms to ensure that data you provide is not lost, misused, or altered inappropriately. These controls include data confidentiality policies and regular database backups.

#### Encryption Policy

Please be aware that the information you send to us in any request forms or in an email message will not be encrypted.

Please do not send any confidential information within clear text forms or email messages.

If you want to provide us confidential information, please contact us at the telephone number given in this policy statement.

### Privacy Policy Changes

We may make changes to our privacy policy to reflect changes in legal and regulatory requirements, or as necessary as we upgrade or modify our technology, applications, and service offerings. We recommend you visit our site to review our privacy policies occasionally.

### Effective Date

December 1, 2009

### Contact

Please contact us at 604.520.6587 if you have a concern regarding this Privacy Policy.
